你在看土著裸女吗
Are you looking at naked tribe's women?
不是  你看
No, look.
这是只猪
That's a pig.
我知道  你看它的咪咪多大
I know, I know, but look at the knobs on her.
艾蜜莉的表弟把我赶出来了
Emily's cousin kicked me out!
什么
What?!
为什么
Why?
老婆的表弟转租公寓给你
Well, when you're subletting an apartment from your wife's cousin
当离婚时
and then you get a divorce,
表弟就会突然把房子要回去
sometimes the cousin suddenly wants his apartment back.
他怎么能这么做  你们没签租约吗
How can he do that? Didn't you sign a lease?
谁跟亲戚租公寓还签租约
Who needs a lease when it's family!
你可以跟我们住
Hey, you can stay with us! We'll take care of ya!
就是啊  只要你需要
Oh, yeah! Absolutely! Anything you need man!
但是你心情好一点了
But you have to promise me you'll let us know the second
就得说一声  好让我们取笑你的鸡窝头
you are feeling better so that we can make fun of your hair!
没问题
You got it.
谢谢  我太感激了
Thanks you guys, I really appreciate this.
我又要去收拾行李了
All right, I'm gonna get packing again.
我最近搬来搬去的
Man, I've been moving around so much lately,
简直像盲流
I'm beginning to feel like a nomad.
-怎么了  -他以为你说你像流氓
- What? - He thought you said gonad.
莫妮卡  假如餐厅都像你这里这么干挣
Wow, Monica, if every restaurant is as clean as yours,
我就失业了
I'd have a tough time making a living.
瞧你说的  莱瑞
Oh, Larry.
卫生稽查员挣佣金的吗
Umm, do health inspectors work on commission?
不  是拿贿赂
No, bribes.
-可以笑吧  -当然  我只是开玩笑
- It's okay to laugh right? - Yeah, I was just kidding.
我去检查厨房地板
I'll check the kitchen floors.
随便查  莱瑞
Okay, knock yourself out, Larry.
帅气
Yum-my!
莱瑞吗
Larry?
我也愿意让他检查我家厨房地板
Oh yeah! I'd let him check out my kitchen floors.
98分
A 98.
你没戴厨师帽  所以扣两分
I deducted 2 points because you are not wearing your chef's hat,
因为违反了第五条规定
and that is a Section 5 violation.
听着  莱瑞  亲爱的
Uh, look, Larry honey,
第五条是我写的
umm, I wrote the book on Section 5
我知道在厨房
and I know that you don't have to wear your hat
才要戴帽子
unless you're in the kitchen.
你的帽子呢
And where is your hat?
在厨房  我进去拿
It's in the kitchen, I'll go get it.
扣两分
Ahh there's the 2 points.
你应该好好读读你写的手册
Hey, you should really read that book you wrote.
你看到帽子在厨房
Wow! You saw the hat in the kitchen
知道她进去时没戴帽子
and you'd know that she'd have to go in there hatless to get it.
你可以开一档卫生稽查侦探节目了
You can have your own health inspector detective show!
你过奖了
Oh, I don't know about that.
那样我就能当你的助手  叫芳达
Yeah, but then I can be you sidekick Vunda.
也许芳达可以给我电话号码
Maybe uh, Vunda could give me her number
我改天约她吃饭
and I can ask her to dinner sometime.
她很乐意
Okay, she would love that!
因为你挑的都是干净馆子
Y'know, since you know all the clean places to eat.
-电话联系  -好的
- I-I'll call ya. - Okay.
他真有趣
He's so funny!
-谢谢  -谢谢你
- Thanks. - Thank you.
莫妮卡  罗斯还好吧
Mon? How's Ross doing?
还在为艾蜜莉伤心吗
Y'know since all the Emily stuff.
心情不太好  不过还死不了
He's not great but he's dealing with it.
等等  你不会想...
Oh wait a minute, you're not gonna try...
亲爱的  拜托
Oh, honey, please, no,
我跟罗斯不可能从头来过了
I can't get started with all that Ross stuff again.
他还会颓废好一阵子的
I mean, he's gonna screwed up for a looong time.
而且你知道
And besides y'know, I don't,
我不追刚离婚的男人
I don't go for guys right after they get divorced.
对  你只追快结婚的男人
Right, you only go for them 5 minutes before they get married.
两磅爪哇摩卡咖啡豆
Two pounds of Moca Java please.
是丹尼
Danny.
你们还会再约会吗
Are you guys ever gonna go out again?
不知道
I don't know!
约会一次后  他就再没给我打过电话
He hasn't called me since that one time when we went out.
我在走廊里碰见他  我们眉来眼去
I see him in the hallway, we flirt,
我笑得花枝乱颤  却没下文
I'm all ha-ha-ha-ha, and nothing.
你们好
Hey!
-你好  丹尼  -哦  很渴对吧
- Hi Danny! - Wow! Thirsty huh?
我周六在家开派对
Uh, actually, actually, I'm having a party at my place on Saturday,
庆祝搬新家
it's sort of a house warming kind of thing.
太好了
Ohh, fun!
真棒
Ohh, great!
我很期待
Yeah, I'm really looking forward to it.
再见
Okay, see ya.
看来他的新家不欢迎我们
Well, I guess we won't be warming his house.
好吧  我知道他在玩什么把戏了
Okay. All right, I see what he's doing!
他不约我  是想让我约他
He's not asking me out, because he wants me to ask him out.
而你不会主动
And you're not gonna do that.
当然  那样他就占上风了
That's right! 'Cause that would give him the control!
所以他借"开派对"
So now he's all ooh, coming up with this whole
为幌子
I've got a party thing y'know,
向我发出邀请的信号
trying to get me to hint around for an invitation.
可是我当场给他好看
Blew up in his face, didn't it?
所以他根本没有要办派对吗
So-so there is no party.
有  当然有
No, there's a party. There's a party.
但是控制权落谁手中
But the power,
依然是未知数
that is still up for grabs.
懂了吗
You follow me?
应该吧
I think so.
你说他喜欢你  所以故意不约你
So, he-he's not inviting you to his party because he likes you.
就是这样
Exactly.
罗斯
Ross?
嗨  室友们
Hey roomies!
你把家里布置得真温馨
Love what you've done with the place.
我知道箱子堆得到处都是
Oh, yeah I know, I know, it's a lot of boxes,
我要再次感谢你们收容我
but again I really appreciate you guys letting me stay here.
应该的
Not a problem.
听我说
And listen, hey!
既然你要在这里住一阵子
Since you're gonna be here for a while, why don't-
干脆在电话留言上加上你好了
I was thinking we uh, put your name on the answering machine.
希望你们别介意
Oh, I uh, hope you don't mind,
但是我已经录了段劲爆的
I kinda already, jazzed it up a little.
你们听
Check it out.
我们一定  一定会回你电话
We will, we will, call you back!
很酷吧
Pretty cool, huh?
你也是假笑吧
You're fake laughing too, right?
不过眼泪是真的
Oh, the tears are real.
你今晚真漂亮
You look beautiful this evening.
再给我看一次徽章
Show me the badge again.
好闪
Shiny.
我去洗个手
Oh, will you mind if I wash up?
下班就直接过来了
Because I came straight from working
谁知道它们摸过哪里
and who knows where these babies have been.
你真会耍宝
You are just nonstop!
我们走
We're outta here!
为什么
Why?!
我刚经过厨房就看到十项违规
Just walking past the kitchen I saw 10 violations!
我要勒令他们停业
I'm shutting this place down!
你有这么大的权利吗
You have the power to do that?
这个有
This does.
那就让他们停业吧
Shut it down.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
没什么
Nothing.
你在建堡垒吗
You built a fort didn't ya?
差不多吧
Kinda.
我的天  空气净化器
Oh my God, the air purifier!
罗斯的空气净化器
Ross's air purifier!
大学四年  我一直听到...
All I heard of 4 years through college was
老兄  你不该只闷在宿舍里
Dude, you should've gone out once and a while.
我讨厌这玩意儿
I hate this thing!
拜托  钱德勒  罗斯是我们的好友
Come on, Chandler, Ross is our friend.
他现在需要我们的帮助
He needs us right now,
所以你为什么不成熟点
so why don't you be a grown up
进堡垒一起看电视吧
and come and watch some TV in the fort!
你好  丹尼
Oh, hi Danny.
我想邀请你们参加明晚的派对
Hey guys, I just uh, wanted to invite you to the party tomorrow night.
多谢  我们有时间就过去
Oh, thanks! We'll try to stop by.
不过我可能有事
Uh, actually, I think I'm gonna be busy.
是吗
You are?
对  我上次跟你说有个庆典
Yeah! Remember I got that uh, gala.
什么庆典
Yeah, what's the gala for?
赛船大会
It's a uh, regatta gala.
是嘛  你会参赛吗
Really! You-you sail?
不会  可是我赞助比赛
No-no, but I support it.
希望明晚能见到你
Okay, hope I see you tomorrow night.
保重
Take care.
我这招让他见识厉害了  不是吗
Walked right into that one didn't he?
哪一招
What one?
你希望他邀你参加派对  他也来啦
You wanted him to invite you to the party and he did it!
可是他等到最后一刻才来
Yeah, but he waited until the last minute!
如果我答应  他就知道我没事可做
So if I said yes, he would know I had nothing better to do
等着被他邀请参加派对
than wait around for an invitation to his stupid party.
但是我说不去  所以还是我占上风
I said, "No!" Which puts me right back in the driver seat.
很好  所以换他出招了吗
Great. So the ball is in his court?
出招  他没招可出了
Ball? No, there is no ball.
乔伊  麻烦你
Joey, please!
对不起
Sorry.
小鬼们
Hello children!
要不要玩桌上足球  拜托
Hey! Wanna play some foosball? Please?
-好的  -不不
- Okay. - No, no.
游戏桌搬进我房间了
We have to move the table into my room, yeah!
因为外面太多箱子  来吧
'Cause of all the boxes. Come on!
我有个问题  这是什么意思
All right, I have one question. What is the deal with this?
小布偶乔伊说再见吗
Bye-bye little puppet Joey hand?
不是  叫我闭嘴的手势
No, the quiet down thing!
你是说这样啊
You mean this.
我不知道我还能忍多久
Look, I-I-I don't know how much more of this I can take!
他竟然拿我的《海滩游侠》录影带
Did you know he taped over my Baywatch tape
去录什么小虫子
with some show about bugs!
天啊  要是里面录的是黄片呢
My God! What if that had been porn?
别激动  或许是很难忍受
All right look, y'know, this maybe tough
可他是罗斯  我跟他大学同寝室四年都没死
but come on, it's Ross! I survived college with him!
好吧  或许我还可以再忍一阵子
All right, I guess I can hold out a little longer.
-来玩吧  -好的
- Let's have a game. - Okay.
-不好  -进了
- No no no! - Yes.
两位
Uh fellas,
他非走不可
Okay, so he's out of here.
这里有没有吃的
You guys got anything to eat?
我刚去强诺店买鸡块  那里停业了
I just went down to Johnos for some chicken and it was closed!
我带莱瑞去  但那里违规太多
Oh, I took Larry there to eat but it was all violated.
所以我们勒令他们停业
So we shut it down!
菲比  如果这家伙不断关掉大家喜欢的餐馆
Pheebs, if this guy keeps closing down all of our favorite places,
以后我们上哪吃饭
where are we gonna eat?!
去干净的地方怎么样
I don't know, clean places?
好好吃
Umm, yum!
是丹尼
It's Danny.
别让他进来  我应该在参加赛船大会
Don't let him in! I'm supposed to be at a regatta gala.
马上就来
We'll be right there!
你不能说赛船大会还没开始吗
Can't you just say it starts later?
哪有赛船大会在晚上举行的
What? What kind of a regatta gala starts at night?!
假的那种
The fake kind!
我想借个勺子  你有吗
Hey, hi, I need a ladle. You got a ladle?
有
We have a ladle.
-谢谢  派对上见  -好的
- Thanks, see you at the party. - Okay.
你们知道莱瑞会怎么回答吗
Hey, you guys, you know what Larry would say?
他会说  "勺后见"
He would say, "See you ladle."
我看完了
Well, I-I-I'm done with this.
你要看吗  罗斯
You want anything Ross?
体育版  国际版  还是租屋版
Sports? International? Apartment listings?
我要体育版
I'll take sports.
我要
Mine!
那就国际版好了
All right. Uhh, international.
我也要
Oh that's mine too!
我老家是意大利
I'm Italian!
那我就看看租屋广告吧
Well, I guess I can check out those apartment listings,
不过报上向来没好屋
even though there's never anything in here.
第七页也没有吗
Not even on page 7?
你说得对
Oh yeah! You're-hey, you're right!
有个地方价钱很公道  两房
Here's an affordable place,  two bedroom,
上班也近  五周后就能搬进去了
close to work, ooh, it's available in five weeks!
圈起来那个呢
What about that circled one?
不知道  就单间来说有点贵
Oh, I-I don't know, it's kind of expensive for a studio.
可是现在就能搬进去  对不对
But it's available now! Isn't it?
的确是
Yes, it is.
我们去看看
Hey, let's go look at it!
-好的  去吧  -我们走
- Okay, let's go. - There we go!
对了  我在想你们是不是
Oh-oh-ooh, hey guys, I was wondering if you guys would uh,
分摊下空气净化器的滤芯的费用
maybe chip in on some new air filters for the purifier?
毕竟净化器大家都有用到
I mean after all, we all are using it.
快点走
Let's go quicker.
天啊
Oh my God!
你们看这个厨房  兼浴室
Yeah, well look at this kitchen, slash bathroom.
太棒了  可以一边煮饭一边洗澡
Well that's great! Y'know so you can cook while in the tub.
房东真是太聪明了
Somebody was using his head.
再看看其它地方
Hey, let's check out the rest of the place.
就这么大了
I think this is it.
算了吧  还是再看看别的公寓
I don't know, maybe we should keep looking.
罗斯  可这地方马上就能搬进来
But hey, Ross, this place is available now!
你不会愿意再跟我们挤五周吧
Yeah, you don't want to be stuck with us for the next five weeks.
你觉得我应该租下吗
So, you-you think I should go ahead and take this place?
这里很棒啊
Oh, it's perfect!
你呢
How about you?
这里有厨房兼浴室哦
It's a kitchen slash bathroom.
我懂你们的意思了
All right, I see what you guys are saying.
我下楼填申请表
I'll uh, I'll go downstairs and fill out an application.
我们是坏人
We are bad people.
他知道我们想赶他走  他知道
He knew we were trying to get rid of him. He knew!
我们家厨房能不能装浴缸
You think we could get a bathtub in our kitchen?
去吃饭  好吗
Hey, ready for dinner?
当然好啊
Ooh, absolutely!
你上次不是说要去
Great! You wanted to go
布里克街那家意大利餐厅吗
the Italian place down on Bleaker Street right?
我爱死那里了
Ooh, I love that place!
所以  不行
So, no.
那去"李赛提老妈"怎么样
How about Mama Lisettie's?
没问题
Enh. Sure!
不知道那盒牛奶放多久了
I wonder how long that milk  has been setting out.
没问题的  这地方非常干净
Oh, no-no, this place is totally healthy!
这盒牛奶是我的
That-this milk is mine.
今天买的  我突然很想喝牛奶
I bought this today, 'cause I was thirsty for milk, y'know.
我们走吧
Okay, let's go!
老兄  卫生条款11-B规定
Hey, buddy!  Are you familiar with Section 11-B of the Health Code
垃圾应该从后门拿出去
that requires all refuse material been taking out the back exit?
可是那样就得从干洗店绕路
But then I'd have to go all the way around the dry cleaner place.
你宁可方便也不顾卫生吗
Oh, so you're saying you'd choose convenience over health?!
莱瑞  别这样
Okay, stop! Larry, okay,
你能不能别老想着工作
can't you just be Larry and not Larry the health inspector guy?
一开始还很刺激
Y'know I mean it was really exciting at first
现在简直是哪家餐厅也去不了
but now it's like, okay, so where are we gonna eat ever?
那我就口头警告他好了
Well, I suppose I could give him a warning.
谢谢
Thank you.
快走啊
Okay, go! Go! Go!
要是吃饱饭后你还想抓人
Now, if after dinner you still really need to bust someone,
我知道有个热狗摊老板喜欢挖鼻子
I know a hot dog vendor who picks his nose.
搞不好我们做的是好事
Maybe, maybe we did a good thing,
帮助罗斯早点恢复正常
helping Ross get back on his feet!
况且那地方实在不错
Yes that was a nice place!
虽然柜子不多
Yeah! Not a lot of closet space,
不过可以用袋子装好东西挂在窗外
but he can just hang his stuff out the window in a bag!
现在该怎么办
What are we gonna do?
不知道  要吃披萨吗
I don't know. Maybe pizza?
我说的是罗斯
About Ross!
喂  是的
Hello, oh, yeah.
是公寓管理员  罗斯填我们当推荐人
It's the apartment manager; Ross put us down as references.
罗斯绝对是好人
Ross is the greatest guy you'll ever meet!
这人非常可靠
Yeah, he's very reliable.
不过他养了一只大狗
Of course he has a big huge dog!
半夜叫个不停
That uh, barks into the night.
谁不喜欢狗呢
Well, who doesn't love dogs?
他是个踢踏舞者
Ah, he's a tap dancer!
是的  这的确是失传的艺术
Yes, some would say that it's a lost art.
他是皮条客
He's a pimp!
没错  就是皮条客
There you go! Yes, he's a pimp.
他是会跳踢踏舞的皮条客
He's a big, tap dancing pimp!
喂
Hello?
这可不行  他就站在那里
This is never gonna work! He's right there!
去打声招呼就行啦
Just go over and say hi.
我得从楼下走上来
No, I have to go downstairs and come back up
假装我刚从赛船大会回来
as if I'm coming home from the regatta gala. Okay?
你去引开他的注意力  但是别勾引他
So just go distract him. But don't be sexy.
丹尼
Hey, Danny!
怎么啦
Hey! What's going on?
这个派对真不错  食物也很好
Oh, it's a great party! Great food.
大部分派对都只有薯片和蘸酱
Y'know, most parties it's all chips and salsa,
薯片和蘸酱
chips and salsa.
那个  这是什么
So umm, what's this?
沙拉
Salad.
这又是什么
And-and-and what-what's this?
面包  你不是厨师吗
Bread. Aren't you a chef?
瑞秋
Hey! Rachel!
是哦  今晚你开派对
Hey! Oh right, tonight was your party.
你看来不错啊  真高兴你赶回来了
Oh wow, you look great! Glad you could make it.
庆典总不能没完没了啊
Oh well, y'know, the gala had to end sometime.
你别走开  我马上回来
Don't go anywhere, I'll be right back.
好的
Yeah, sure.
你说现在换谁出招啦
All right, whose court is the ball in now?
你不是说他没招可出吗
I thought there wasn't a ball?
拜托  他很高兴我来了
Oh, come on! He's glad that I came,
而且还叫我别走开
he doesn't want me to go anywhere,
我们两个现在是你来我住
balls flying all over the place!
瑞秋  这是我朋友汤姆
Rachel, this is my friend Tom.
这就是我跟你提过的小姐
This is the girl I told you about.
不是吧  你跟人提过我
Oh, go on! You telling people about me?
你们一定会来电  我去招呼客人了
You two could really hit it off! I'm gonna go mingle.
你在布明岱尔百货上班吗
So you work at Bloomingdale's, huh?
我妈管那里叫"布明儿"
My mom calls it Bloomies.
稍息  大兵
Yeah, okay, at ease solider!
什么
I'm sorry?
没关系  你别装了  汤米
No, it's all right, you can just drop the act Tommy.
我知道你们搞什么鬼
I know what's going on here.
你是丹尼的好友对不对
You're Danny's wingman right?
你们交情老  感情好
You guys are best buds. Frat bros!
我还是去找朋友聊好了
I'm gonna go talk to uh, a friend.
请便  去找你朋友吧
Yeah, yeah, you go talk to your friend.
告诉他  "这招漂亮"
You tell him, "Nice try."
他真是出招连连
Man! He just keeps lobbing them up
不过我可是招招都破
and I just keep knocking them right out of the park!
-我想喝一杯  -我也是
- I think I need a drink. - Yeah.
九十八  九十九
98. 99.
一百
100.
走吧
Okay, go!
告诉你  我没问题
Dude, I'm telling ya! I'm fine!
我扶住你了
Here we go! Here we go!
我没租到那间公寓
Hey. So I uh, I didn't get that apartment.
我的申请出了点问题
Some problem with my application.
-不是吧  -不是吧  怎么会呢
- You're kidding! - You're kidding, no!
不过好消息是
Yeah. But, the good news is
菲比答应让我搬去跟她住
that Phoebe said that I could stay at her place for a while. So...
罗斯  你不能住菲比家  我们可是室友
But you can't stay with Phoebe, Ross! We're-we're roomies!
我不能再占用你们的地方了
Look, you guys don't need me here taking up all your space.
反正这里大得很
Well, we got plenty of space!
喇叭旁边还有空地
There-there's still some over there by-by that speaker.
住下来吧
Please, just stay!
你们确定吗
Are you guys sure about this?
当然
Definitely!
罗斯  你非住下来不可
Yes! Ross, you have to stay!
-好的  -太好了  哥们
- All right. - All right, buddy.
我是皮条客吗
So I'm a pimp huh?
算了
It's okay!
我知道我有时候很讨人厌
Look, I know that sometimes I can be a pain in the ass,
不过你们可以直接告诉我
but you just have to talk to me.
哪里做得不好  行吗
Tell me if something is bothering you. Okay?
我可以尽量改掉
And for my part I'll really do everything I can
讨人嫌的习惯  你们只要...
to keep my annoying habits just you know...
显然你今天过得很充实
Well, I see you've had a very productive day.
你不觉得戴牛仔帽太夸张了吗
Don't you think the cowboy hat is a little much?
进来吧  很好玩
Come on, it's fun!
好吧
All right!
这不是女人的帽子吗
Isn't this a woman's hat?
哥们  还不赶快闭嘴去泡茶
Dude, stop talking crazy and make us some tea!